Mr. Fu
These are what I kept from back then
Speak
15 years ago near Qinghe Orphanage
I met an injured boy
It was raining that day
He was leaning by the road
With an injured wrist
I had someone take him to the community hospital
He dropped this pendant then
I've kept it ever since
How old were you then
Around 10
Wrong, he wasn't in Nancheng at all that year
Which hospital was it
Nancheng Third Community Hospital
Who signed as the companion
Sister
Do you think I'm lying
I haven't said anything yet
Su Yurou, bring out the originals
What originals
The original hospital receipt
And the pendant
You said you've always kept it
You should know where it was originally kept
Mr. Fu, Mr. Qin is here
Where did these come from
Mr. Qin, these are what I kept when I saved
Mr. Fu back then
You were the one who saved him
Then bring out the originals